Finding Aid for the Jonathan Friedlander Collection of Middle Eastern Americana LSC.1314
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound Recordings, 1950 - 2005; 5 oversize boxes
  - Phonograph records, 1950 - 2003; 5 oversize boxes
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Epic., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Parliament., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Parliament., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Creator: Chalabala, Zdenek
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Parliament., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Creator: Czech Philharmonic Orchestra
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Media, PA: Somerset Records., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Media, PA: Somerset Records., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Creator: Rörh, Wilhelm
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Media, PA: Somerset Records., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Creator: North German Symphony Orchestra
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Columbia., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Creator: Rodzinski, Artur
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Columbia., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Columbia., ca. 1950s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Long Island City, NY: Pickwick., ca. 1970s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Creator: Steinberg, William
      Cover is a photograph of a woman in belly dancing costume.
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Long Island City, NY: Pickwick., ca. 1970s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Long Island City, NY: Pickwick., ca. 1970s; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Creator: Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Philips., ca. 1972; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Cover illustration by Elly Griepink-Meijer, Goor, Holland.
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Philips., ca. 1972; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Creator: Haitink, Bernard
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Philips., ca. 1972; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Philips., ca. 1972; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Creator: Griepink-Meijer, Elly
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Camden, NJ: RCA Victor., ca. 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Creator: Stokowski, Leopold
      Cover features an illustration of Scheherazade reclined at the feet of King Shahryar.
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Camden, NJ: RCA Victor., ca. 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Creator: Philharmonic Orchestra of London
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Camden, NJ: RCA Victor., ca. 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Columbia., undated; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Cover photograph is a woman dressed as Scheherazade.
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Columbia., undated; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: Columbia., undated; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Newark, NJ: Regent., undated; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Creator: Regent Symphony Orchestra
      Cover is a photo of St. Basil's Cathedral, Moscow, Russia.
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Newark, NJ: Regent., undated; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 Newark, NJ: Regent., undated; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Creator: Federer, Alfred
    - Shéhérazade CBS Records Masterworks., 1984; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Creator: Boulez, Pierre
      Cover design by Christopher Lione. Texts and lyrics enclosure.
    - Shéhérazade CBS Records Masterworks., 1984; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Creator: BBC Symphony Orchestra
    - Shéhérazade CBS Records Masterworks., 1984; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Creator: Crespin, Régine
      Cover painting is "Death of Sardanapalus" by Eugene Delacroix, courtesy of Musée du Louvre, Paris.
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Creator: Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869
      Cover painting is "Death of Sardanapalus" by Eugene Delacroix, courtesy of Musee du Louvre, Paris.
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Creator: Danco, Suzanne
      Texts and translations enclosed.
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Creator: Paris Conservatoire Orchestra
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Creator: Johnson, Thor
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Creator: Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Shéhérazade and Nuits d'été New York, NY: London Records., 1976; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Creator: Ansermet, Ernest, 1883-1969
    - Sheik Yerbouti Salem, MA: BMG., 1979; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Cover features a photograph of Frank Zappa wearing a keffiyeh.
    - Sherwin M. Goldman presents Nefertiti New York, NY: Take Home Tunes., 1978; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Creator: Spangler, David
      Cover is an illustration of Nefertiti. Album design by Tom McLain.
    - Slave to the power: the Iron Maiden tribute Dortmund, Germany: People Like You Records., 2003; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Cover painting, featuring Egyptian pyramids and funerary relics, by Chris Cooper.
    - Sodom and Gomorrah original sound track recording Lomita, CA: Cambria., 1962; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Special limited re-issue for Sumiya LTD, Tokyo.
    - Solomon and Sheba an original sound track recording Universal City, Calif.: MCA., 1959; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Cover is an illustration of Yul Brynner and Gina Lollobrigida as Solomon and Sheba.
    - Solomon and Sheba an original sound track recording Universal City, Calif.: MCA., 1959; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Sons of the desert Anaheim, CA: Mark 56 Records., 1975; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Creator: Hatley, Marvin
      Cover features a photograph of Stan Laurel and Oliver Hardy dressed as Shriners.
    - Sons of the desert Anaheim, CA: Mark 56 Records., 1975; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Creator: Laurel, Stan
    - Sons of the desert Anaheim, CA: Mark 56 Records., 1975; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Creator: Hardy, Oliver
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: RCA., 1958; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Creator: San Francisco Symphony Orchestra
      Cover is a photographic depiction of Scheherazade at the feet of King Shahryar.
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: RCA., 1958; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Scheherazade, opus 35 New York, NY: RCA., 1958; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Shéhérazade Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1986; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Creator: Baker, Janet
      Cover painting is "The Harem" by Juan Gimenez-Martin, courtesy of The Bridgeman Art Library.
    - Shéhérazade Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1986; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Creator: New Philharmonic Orchestra
    - Shéhérazade Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1986; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Creator: Barbirolli, John
    - Shéhérazade Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1986; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Shéhérazade and Le mort de Cléopâtre New York, NY: Columbia., 1963; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Shéhérazade and Le mort de Cléopâtre New York, NY: Columbia., 1963; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Shéhérazade and Le mort de Cléopâtre New York, NY: Columbia., 1963; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Creator: Berlioz, Hector
    - Shéhérazade and Le mort de Cléopâtre New York, NY: Columbia., 1963; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Sheherazade and Polovtsian dances New York, NY: London Records, 1982., 1961; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Cover painting is "Odalisque" by Auguste Renoir, courtesy of the National Gallery of Art, Washington, Chester Dale Collection.
    - Sheherazade and Polovtsian dances New York, NY: London Records, 1982., 1961; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Sheherazade and Polovtsian dances New York, NY: London Records, 1982., 1961; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Sheherazade and Polovtsian dances New York, NY: London Records, 1982., 1961; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Strictly belly dancing New York, NY: Scepter Records., 1973; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Creator: Kochak, Eddie
      Cover is a photo of Eddie "the Sheik" Kochak with the Ibrahim Dance Company. Excerpt from back cover reads, "Professional belly dancers will welcome it, but it was also produced especially appealing to the new craze of using this medium of physical coordination towards obtaining the beautiful figure, posture, and poise, so in demand by students, housewives, secretaries, etc..."
    - Strictly belly dancing New York, NY: Scepter Records., 1973; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Creator: Obadia, Hakki
    - Strictly belly dancing volume three New York, NY: Ameraba Records., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Cover is a photo of Eddie "the Sheik" Kochak and dancer Habeeba from Dance of the Art Incorporated, Columbus, Ohio. Excerpt from back cover reads, "In this album all of the sensual enchanting and exciting tempos and rhythms have been musically magnified and enhanced by Eddie's intuitive understanding of Middle East Belly Dance Music."
    - Strictly belly dancing volume three New York, NY: Ameraba Records., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Strictly belly dancing volume two New York, NY: Ameraba Records (West End Music Industries)., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Cover is a photo of Eddie "the Sheik" Kochak, Hakki Obadia, and dancer Phaedra from the Ibrahim Farrah Near East Dance Group.
    - Strictly belly dancing volume two New York, NY: Ameraba Records (West End Music Industries)., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Creator: Kassab, Joseph
    - Strictly belly dancing volume two New York, NY: Ameraba Records (West End Music Industries)., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Suspicion Los Angeles, CA: Geffen., 1987; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Creator: Gene Loves Jezebel (Musical group)
      Cover features an illustration of Isis.
    - Symphony no. 2, op. 9 (Antar) New York: RCA Victor., 1968; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Creator: Marvin, Fredric
      Cover painting by Frederic Marvin features Scheherazade and King Shahryar.
    - Symphony no. 2, op. 9 (Antar) New York: RCA Victor., 1968; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Symphony no. 2, op. 9 (Antar) New York: RCA Victor., 1968; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Creator: Gould, Morton
    - Symphony no. 2, op. 9 (Antar) New York: RCA Victor., 1968; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Creator: Myaskovski, Nikolai
    - Symphony no. 2, op. 9 (Antar) New York: RCA Victor., 1968; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Symphony number 2 opus 9, Antar Capriccio espagnol Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1974; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Cover art by Mizue Hamiltono.
    - Symphony number 2 opus 9, Antar Capriccio espagnol Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1974; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Creator: Ivanov, Konstantin
    - Symphony number 2 opus 9, Antar Capriccio espagnol Hollywood, CA: Angel., 1974; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Creator: Moscow Radio Symphony Orchestra
    - Taras Bulba original music from the motion picture New York, NY: United Artists., 1962; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Creator: Waxman, Franz, 1906-1967
      Cover is a depiction of Yul Brynner posed as Ukrainian Cossack Colonel Taras Bulba, Tony Curtis as Andrei Bulba, and Christine Kauffman as Natalia Dubrov.
    - Taras Bulba original music from the motion picture New York, NY: United Artists., 1962; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Ten commandments original motion picture score Los Angeles, CA: United., 1966; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Thamos, König in Ägypten KV 345 Hamburg, Germany: Teldec., 1981; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Creator: Concertgebouw Orchestra
      Includes lyric sheet.
    - Thamos, König in Ägypten KV 345 Hamburg, Germany: Teldec., 1981; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Creator: Harnoncourt, Nikolaus
    - Thamos, König in Ägypten KV 345 Hamburg, Germany: Teldec., 1981; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Creator: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
    - Desert song and The student prince New York, NY: Monmouth-Evergreen., ca. 1973; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches, 2 copies (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Includes operetta excerpts.
    - Theme from Exodus and other great themes Newark, NJ: Pirouette., 1961; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 11)
      Creator: Stradivari Strings
    - Themes from the score of Cecil B. De Mille's Samson and Delilah, a Paramount picture themes from John Ford's Technicolor production The quiet man, a Republic picture Los Angeles, CA: Varese Sarabande., 1957; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Thief of Baghdad Film Music Collection, FMC-8., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Creator: Saltarello Choir
    - Thief of Baghdad Film Music Collection, FMC-8., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Thief of Baghdad Film Music Collection, FMC-8., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Creator: Miklós Rózsa, 1907-
    - Thief of Baghdad Film Music Collection, FMC-8., 1977; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Thief of Baghdad Warner Brothers., 1978; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Thief of Baghdad Warner Brothers., 1978; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Thief of Baghdad Warner Brothers., 1978; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Thief of Baghdad Warner Brothers., 1978; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Verdi: Aïda Camden, NJ: RCA Victor., 1952; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Cover features the face of a pharaonic sarcophagus.
    - Verdi: Aïda Camden, NJ: RCA Victor., 1952; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Verdi: Aïda Camden, NJ: RCA Victor., 1952; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Walt Disney presents famous arias from Aida and other operas Disneyland., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Creator: Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883
      Cover is an illustration of a man in pharoanic dress.
    - Walt Disney presents famous arias from Aida and other operas Disneyland., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Creator: Camarata, Salvadore, 1913-
    - Walt Disney presents famous arias from Aida and other operas Disneyland., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Walt Disney presents famous arias from Aida and other operas Disneyland., 1964; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Creator: Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924
    - Wildest dreams Hollywood, CA: AEI Records., 1981; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Wildest dreams Hollywood, CA: AEI Records., 1981; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 17)
      Creator: Reynolds, Dorothy
    - Wind and the lion original soundtrack recording New York, NY: Arista., 1975; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, stereo, 12 inches (Box 39, Folder 18)
      Cover features an illustration of Sean Connery as a Berber chieftan and his captive, Candice Bergen as Eden Pedecaris.
  - Compact discs, 1984 - 2005; 1 oversize box
    This subseries consists of compact discs (CDs), primarily popular music albums and compilations such as belly dance music.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    SUBSERIES CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - One thousand and one nights Music Moods., 2001; 1 sound disc: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39)
      Creator: Various Artists
      1. One Thousand and One Nights (Alf Leyla We Leyla)
      2. Where Do We Begin (Hikaya)
      3. Move Your Belly
      4. Love Night (Leilat Hob)
      5. Beginning
      6. Sandstorm (Sinbad)
      7. One Thousand and One Nights (Alf Leyla We Leyla) [Club Version]
      8. Disturb (Izaaj)
    - One thousand and one nights Music Moods., 2001; 1 sound disc: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39)
      Creator: Mrad, Said
    - Bellydance overdrive Mondo Melodia., 2004; 1 sound disc: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39, Folder 19)
      Creator: Turbo Tabla (Musical group)
      Track listing:
      1. Longa H.K.K
      2. Zaynab
      3. Dulab Rast
      4. Ya Shadil Al-han
      5. Turbo Tabla 3
      6. Telegrafin Telleri
      7. Mahbub
      8. Allahu Ya'aalim
      9. Shred
      10. Longa Farahfaza
      11. Hat Ayyuha Saqi
      12. Pedro Abdallah
      13. Turbo Tabla 2
    - Desert roses 3 Mondo Melodia., 2004; 1 sound disc: digital, 4 3/4 inches (disc missing) (Box 39, Folder 20)
      Track Listing:
      1. Walk Like An Egyptian - Hakim
      2. Hanina - Steve Stevens
      3. Ajaja - Ramses
      4. Un Ange En Paix - Amina
      5. El Wala Wala - Hakim
      6. Zazarkhatri - Cheb Mami
      7. Elli Tmanetoh (Galactic Mix) - Nawal Al Zoghbi
      8. Begharamak Masloube - Woroud
      9. Niloufareh Bahar - Andy
      10. Mahbub - Turbo Tabla
      11. Akadt Aalik Gualbi - Cheb Nasro
      12. Who's The Fairest - Shani
    - i am... Sony Music., 1999; 1 sound disc: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39, Folder 21)
      Creator: Jones, Nasir
      Cover features artist made up as a mummy.
      1. Intro
      2. N.Y. State Of Mind (Part II)
      3. Hate Me Now - (featuring Puff Daddy)
      4. Small World
      5. Favor For A Favor - (featuring Scarface)
      6. We Will Survive
      7. Ghetto Prisoners
      8. You Won't See Me Tonight - (featuring Aaliyah)
      9. I Want To Talk To You
      10. Dr. Knockboot
      11. Life Is What You Make It - (featuring DMX)
      12. Big Things
      13. Nas Is Like
      14. K-I-SS-I-N-G
      15. Money Is My Bitch
    - Latin American hits for bellydance ARC Music Productions., 2001; 2 sound discs: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39, Folder 22)
      Creator: Ramzy, Hossam
      CD 1
      1. Chachita - 4:54
      2. Palo Palito - 4:12
      3. Guantanamera - 4:19
      4. El Porompompero - 4:25
      5. Ciclito Lindo - 5:01
      6. La Malagueña - 3:29
      7. Besame Mucho - 3:16
      8. La Cucaracha - 3:52
      9. La Bamba - 3:47
      10. Arabia Azteca - 6:35
      CD 2
      1. Conga - 4:26
      2. Moliendo Café - 4:11
      3. Maracaibo - 4:32
      4. No Sé-No Sé - 3:53
      5. Cuando Calienta el Sol - 4:06
      6. Bamboleo - 5:00
      7. Delicado - 4:37
      8. Eo-Tchan - 4:59
      9. Mas Que Nada - 6:09
      10. Ave María No Morro - 5:08
    - Latin American hits for bellydance ARC Music Productions., 2001; 2 sound discs: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39, Folder 22)
      Creator: Carmaco, Pablo
    - Lucifer rising White Dog Music., 2005; 2 sound discs: digital, 4 3/4 inches (Box 39, Folder 23)
      Creator: Beausoleil, Bobby
      Film soundtrack.
      1. Lucifer Rising, Pt. 1
      2. Lucifer Rising, Pt. 2
      3. Lucifer Rising, Pt. 3
      4. Lucifer Rising, Pt. 4
      5. Lucifer Rising, Pt. 5
      6. Lucifer Rising, Pt. 6